virtualpbx.com 2008-06-16

# Privacy For a Wireless Business Phone System, Wireless PBX, and 1 800 Phone Numbers

VirtualPBX.com, Inc.® respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Online Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices relating to information we gather through this Web site. 

## The Information We Collect

The information gathered by VirtualPBX.com generally falls into two categories: (1) information supplied by visitors to the site when they register or initiate transactions, and (2) tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through the VirtualPBX.com site. Third-party providers, whose sites are featured on and accessed via our site, may gather information as well.

The information you provide us during a visit to VirtualPBX.com helps us to improve the quality and utility of our site. The more information you share with us, the better we can serve your needs.

When you purchase Virtual PBX® services, we request the following types of information on our order form:

  * Name 
  * Shipping and/or billing address 
  * Credit card number or account number 
  * Phone or fax number 
  * Email address 
  * Date of birth 
  * Social Security Number 
  * Driver's license number 

For corporate accounts, we may also request one or more of the following types of information:

  * Federal Tax ID 
  * Company name 
  * Other information your employer may ask us to collect, such as purchase order number, employee number, and the like 

We need this information to process your order. If we have trouble processing your order, the contact information you provide is used to get in touch with you. We also use this contact information to provide you with updates regarding your current phone or service.

For new accounts, we may request a Social Security Number, which we use to order a credit report. The only other purpose for which we'll use your Social Security Number is to confirm your identity when you inquire about or access your account.

To take advantage of personalized services available on VirtualPBX.com, you may need to supply additional information, such as: 

  * Virtual PBX® Number 
  * Level of responsibility for account administration 

We use this data to provide you with billing information, equipment discounts, and rate plan promotions. 

## Email Addresses

If you provide us your email address, from time to time we may send you emails about new products and services, or offers that we believe will interest you. We may also share your email address with providers of products or services that we think will interest you. Though we hope you'll find this information useful, if you do not wish to receive such email, please indicate, when you give us your email address, that you'd prefer not to receive such information or offers. We will also use your email address to answer any email you send us, or to follow up on your visit to VirtualPBX.com. Such follow-ups may include inquiries on transactions or submissions of information that appear incomplete. Of course, you can always elect not to receive future emails by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link that we include in all of the emails we send. 

## Cookies

To help us tailor our site to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a small entry in a text file, called a cookie, on your hard drive. The cookie contains an ID number that allows us to track the pages you've visited. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs of our users. The help function on most browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don't accept cookies, you won't be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors. 

## Browser Level Information

Our Web server automatically collects your IP address when you request pages from our server. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. We also collect information on the operating system you're running on your computer and the Web browser software you're using to access our site so we can optimize our site for the most popular operating systems and Web browsers. And, because we like to know how you found our site, we keep track of where you came from. 

## Pop-up Surveys

From time to time, we request information from users via pop-up surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary; if you don't want to provide the requested information, please don't respond to the survey. The information we gather through these surveys will be used to improve our site. 

## Information Collected by Third Parties

Of course, our site includes links to other Web sites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another Web site or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our Web site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting or the provider of such products or services. The provider's privacy practices may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our provider partners via a link either from the site's home page or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information. 

## Security

The information we collect from our visitors is stored in databases we control. Physical access to the servers on which we store visitor information is restricted. We use your credit card information only to bill you for the products and services you order from us. We don't share your credit card information with anyone, except as may be necessary to process your transactions. To protect the privacy of your credit card number and other ordering information, we encrypt this information for transit over the Internet using a Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") connection. However, as effective as modern security practices are, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet.

Most Web browsers allow use of an SSL connection. If your browser does not support use of an SSL connection, or if you prefer not to send your credit card number over the Internet, you can place your order by calling us toll free at 1-888-825-0800. 

## Disclosure of Information

We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Visitor Agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, our customers, the public or VirtualPBX.com, Inc. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that VirtualPBX.com, Inc, one of its business units, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by another company, information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets. 

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is subject to change. The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the new policy promptly. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what was stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you and give you an opportunity to opt out of the proposed use. By using VirtualPBX.com, you agree that your visit to our site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by the then-current version of the Online Privacy Policy. 

_This Online Privacy Policy was last revised on February 8, 2006._
